http://teststeststests.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy TestsTestsTests.com
HomeMicrosoft Office IndexExcelWordPowerPointA~Z QuizzesComputer ProgrammingTyping IndexTyping Speed TestEnglish Lessons & Practice Grammar TestsExcel 2016Word 2016
Privacy Policy - TestsTestsTests.com
TestsTestsTests.com respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information that you provide to us. This statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure of your personal information by TestsTestsTests.com. Please note that, TestsTestsTests.com reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how TestsTestsTests.com collects and uses personal information. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by TestsTestsTests.com as explained below.
Personal Information
You have complete control over your personal information. In general, you can visit our web site without providing us with any personal information. However, there are instances where we must have your personal information in order for to send you newsletters, reply to your emails or send you products. This information may include registration data (your name, address, email address, phone number, title, etc.), information request data and response data ("User Information"). When you receive your confirmation email or when you receive any email from the list server, you will be given instructions on how to remove yourself from the list.
Use of User Information
We intend to use such information for purposes of supporting your
relationship with TestsTestsTests.com by designing a web site content that is suitable for your needs and alerting you to new website content, new product and service offerings as they become available. This User Information may be retained by TestsTestsTests.com to verify compliance with the agreement between TestsTestsTests.com and you, to keep track of the domains from which people visit us, to create a user profile to better serve you, or to simply contact you either electronically or otherwise. If you decide that we should not use your personal User Information to contact you, please let us know and we will not use that information for such purposes. Please do not submit any User Information if you are less than 18 years of age.
Disclosure of User Information
TestsTestsTests.com does not sell, trade, transfer or disclose User Information to third parties unless required to by law (e.g. a court order).
Accuracy and Security.
The accuracy and security of the User Information is important to TestsTestsTests.com. Currently, you may review and request updates to your User Information retained by contacting TestsTestsTests.com. If you contact us to correct your User Information, we will attempt to correct such inaccuracies in a timely manner. TestsTestsTests.com is concerned with the security of your User Information and is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access and use of that personal information.
Usernames and Passwords
Access to certain content on our web site may be allowed under a written agreement between you or your employer and TestsTestsTests.com and will require a username and/or password. In some cases, failure to provide personal information may prevent you from accessing certain TestsTestsTests.com web site features containing certain confidential information, products, services, or promotional offers. By accessing and using our protected and secured web site, you agree to maintain the confidentiality of the username and password you selected to access TestsTestsTests.com and consent to our Terms of Use.
Cookies
TestsTestsTests.com uses "cookies". A cookie is a small data file that a web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to keep records of the visits to such site. A cookie contains information such as your username and password that helps us recognize the pages you have visited and improve future visits, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is the information that you provide yourself. A cookie cannot read data off of your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Information stored in cookies may be encrypted, however, we do not store your credit card number in cookies. If you prefer not to accept a cookie, you can set your web browser
to warn you before accepting cookies or you can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your web browser. However, access to some of our secured web site may require the use of cookies, which you must enable only cookies that get sent back to the originating server. Otherwise, you can still access most of the features on our web site even without accepting a cookie.
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads to TestsTestsTests.com based on a user's prior
website visits. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to website users based on visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. For more information on how Google uses data when you visit the TestsTestsTests.com website click here.
External Links
TestsTestsTests.com web site provides links to other third party web sites. Even if the third party is affiliated with TestsTestsTests.com through a business partnership or otherwise, TestsTestsTests.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk.
If you have any issues with sites TestsTestsTests.com links to or any advertisement on TestsTestsTests.com we would like to hear about it. TestsTestsTests.com blocks various kinds of advertising
(gambling, dating, cosmetic procedures, weight loss, get rich quick, black magic, sex and sexuality, religion, guns and firearms and more) but from time to time we have found some of these ads appearing on our website anyway. Different ads appear in different countries and it is difficult to monitor every ad served. If you find any such advertisement or an offensive advertisement on our website we would appreciate you sending a screenshot of the ad to howdy@teststeststests.com . TestsTestsTests.com will review and possibly remove the advertiser or advertisement and/or link.
Terms of Use
Please also see our Terms of Use, which describes the restrictions, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire TestsTestsTests.com web site.
General
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please contact TestsTestsTests.com via our Contact page.
